So friends how are you all I
hope everything is fine and as I was
going towards you guys that the
technique I tell you is how to enter the stock market and
how to invest in shares
and I am telling you
that I have four to five points in
which one is Dam 999 which is from 99999 the
concept of accused is one of the
dates last year and see the profit of the company and from
which you should get everything on
this basis we have made a message on the top of this
and will share it with you it is only a few
days before
predicting the points you should
not do any kind of instruction
use your own intelligence and
accordingly you should invest in the stock market so let's go to
your computer
screen and our website and if we talk then
you can see our religion battery
statement is checked
I am ready to bounce back to work so
this is for the qualities and for power and cement
companies subscribe and do
not forget to subscribe and subscribe to this channel
subscribe as well as this  The point is this
and subscribe for distribution companies,
then press this subscribe
so that you
get notifications of upcoming videos first, so
let's start as I have
told you, now you can see this
in our market, subscribe and
subscribe if I do this, then this
subscribe is
for a very good company and this is a
very good one, we will
talk about ourselves, the problem is quite
normal 10807, so in this way it is
very good and
as we say most and
excuse me parameter which is two day
moving average and one week feedback moving
average, now see the stock as per today,
this freedom in stock, this seven six to avoid
amazing, by the time this seven four five will
subscribe, then companies will
subscribe if you subscribe crore
but appointed etc. so this is
our Ghaghra subscribe
that now see the operating profit, it kept increasing since June 2018
and after this
because people and subscribe to it
and appointed
operating profit of last year  If you look at the net profit, then
excluding this, the appointed subscribe
because by appointing the subscribe company,
now the engine is yaar, this is March-2011
subscribe, this has decreased every year
and now the school and subscribe
subscribe to, if
you look at the same report, it is quite
big, from 255 crores, if you look at it now, it is 873
crores, but we can see that their
profit has also increased four times from 127 crores in 2010, it is
6.7 crores now,
Dhindsa's profit is the
problem, after this the profit of this company was
500 crores in 2010, which has increased to
4000-10 crores, which
in eight-ten years the company has grown eight times,
which is very good and this
company is now the school, the expenditure on it, so
in this directly you will see that
it has given good returns in the case of youth, then keep your subscribe, then
keep the screen brightness very low, so
everything is good,
I do not feel bad about anything about it, and
after this  If we live here, then look at this picture, in
June 2000,
in March 2019, the stake of Johnson
Controls and Motors
was 22%
and this family, they
left their investments and subscribed here
but they are subscribed
and this is what you will see in the public, if you
want to see how weak then this Panther, this Bell
Folding, after that, which
I had left, they have folded in schools from here
and this is very enough,
so according to me, in the next six months in this city,
we can easily earn 30 to 40 percent,
this is my research, you should
invest only after doing your research, keep investing, keep
studying.